const quizData = [
    {
      "label": 1,
      "question": "What AI stands for?",
      "options": ["Air Isolation ", "Army Innovation", "Automated intelligence", "Artificial Intelligence"],
      "answer": "Artificial Intelligence"
    },
    {
      "label": 2,
      "question": "Do you know who founded BitHubAi company?",
      "options": ["Omid Panahi","Mark B. Fisher", "Satoshi Nakamoto", "Jeff Bozos"],
      "answer": "Omid Panahi" 
    },
    {
      "label": 3,
      "question": "What is the goal of AI?",
      "options": ["To understand human emotions", "To mimic human intelligence", "To build rockets", "To grow vegetables"],
      "answer": "To mimic human intelligence"
    },
    {
      "label": 4,
      "question": "Why do we use AI?",
      "options": ["To play games", "To make coffee", "To automate tasks", "To bake cakes"],
      "answer": "To automate tasks"
    },
    {
      "label": 5,
      "question": "Which one makes more sense when using AI?",
      "options": ["Cooking recipes", "Driving cars", "Singing songs", "Flying kites"],
      "answer": "Driving cars"
    },
    {
      "label": 6,
      "question": "Who painted the Mona Lisa?",
      "options": ["Vincent Van Gogh", "Leonardo da Vinci", "Pablo Picasso", "Claude Monet"],
      "answer": "Leonardo da Vinci"
    },
    {
      "label": 7,
      "question": "Which problem does Artificial Intelligence try to solve?",
      "options": ["By making us smarter", "By predicting weather", "By washing dishes", "By ordering pizza"],
      "answer": "By predicting weather"
    },
    {
      "label": 8,
      "question": "What is the purpose of AI?",
      "options": ["To make us laugh", "To cure diseases", "To build sandcastles", "To teach mathematics"],
      "answer": "To cure diseases"
    },
    {
      "label": 9,
      "question": "Which of these companies was not founded in a garage?",
      "options": ["Amazon", "Google", "Apple", "Microsoft"],
      "answer": "Amazon"
    },
    {
      "label": 10,
      "question": "What do we call a computer program that learns from data?",
      "options": ["AI", "ML", "DL", "RL"],
      "answer": "ML"
    },
    {
      "label": 11,
      "question": "Which of the following is an example of Learning from data?",
      "options": ["Calculator", "Toaster", "Robot", "Television"],
      "answer": "Robot"
    },
    {
      "label": 12,
      "question": "Which city is the capital of France?",
      "options": ["Nance", "Paris", "London", "Amsterdam"],
      "answer": "Paris"
    },
    {
      "label": 13,
      "question": "Which of the following is an example of automated assistance in daily life?",
      "options": ["Microwave", "Refrigerator", "Smartphone", "Pencil"],
      "answer": "Smartphone"
    },
    {
      "label": 14,
      "question": "What do we call the mysterious regions in space where gravity is so strong that not even light can escape?",
      "options": ["White holes", "Dark matter", "Black holes", "Supernovas"],
      "answer": "Black holes"
    },
    {
      "label": 15,
      "question": "Which of these companies has a radical human mimic program?",
      "options": ["Amazon", "Google", "Apple", "Microsoft"],
      "answer": "Google"
    },
    {
      "label": 16,
      "question": "In the field of quantum mechanics, what term describes the state where a particle can exist in multiple states simultaneously?",
      "options": ["Quantum leap", "Quantum entanglement", "Quantum superposition", "Quantum tunneling"],
      "answer": "Quantum superposition"
    },
    {
      "label": 17,
      "question": "What is the capital of France?",
      "options": ["New York", "London", "Paris", "Dublin"],
      "answer": "Paris"
    },
    {
      "label": 18,
      "question": "What is the largest planet in our solar system?",
      "options": ["Earth", "Jupiter", "Saturn", "Mars"],
      "answer": "Jupiter"
    },
    {
      "label": 19,
      "question": "Did you answer the same question twice?",
      "options": ["No","Yes","Maybe","I don't know"],
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "label": 20,
      "question": "Do you think I am a smart AI application asking you these questions based on your general information?",
      "options": ["Yes", "No"],
      "answer": "Yes" 
    }
  ];
  
  export default quizData;
  